Connect Zana Mobile to your computer.
On your computer, open Settings, then Remote access. Select Get a connect code.
Sign in with GitHub, then choose your subdomain.
Reserve the address, then copy your code.
Return to Zana and paste the code. Your computer connects automatically.
Once your computer is connected, open Settings, then Phone. Scan the QR code with your iPhone camera.
Accept the TestFlight invitation and install Zana. Then open the app.
Now open Zana Mobile. Tap Continue with GitHub, and use the same account as your computer.
In the browser, tap Approve phone. Then tap Return to Zana Mobile.
Choose your computer from the list, and tap Connect.
You’re connected. Follow your agents from the mobile kanban, with their status at a glance.
Keep Zana running, and your computer awake and online.